This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
Speed 85 aisles per hour.
Six seven eight.
88 aisles.
12 minutes remaining.
We'll be crossing the
deadline in 10 minutes, sir.
We only have 12 minutes.
Give it spectacular wings.
You and Your men are all
going to die along with us.
You think so, huh?
You're wrong there.
We're perfectly prepared for this.
Here's to an absolutely
beautiful rendezvous.
Ha!
Listen up!
He's a blonde man in a red coat.
Come on!
Jeez, this place is crawling
with those bad lads.
Man, this just isn't my day.
I'm stuck.
Now what am I supposed to do?
Hey, you.
Huh?
Tell me something.
Why'd you save me? Ow!
Ooh, that hurt.
What you really mean to say is thank
you for saving me, isn't that right?
Uh, yeah, whatever you say.
Okay, Mr.
Know-It-All, what are the
baddie laddies gonna do now?
Well it's not good you mean into
the canyon they're gonna drop the
steamer oh man why can't i just get
a break death and poverty like me so
much they brought friends oh yeah
and then there's the insurance girls
it never ends ow why why did i say
that why did i say it was my dad's ship
shit why do i even care
about this stupid rig
my dad was just a good
for nothing workaholic
All right!
Okay, time to get going.
Well, can I at least
ask where we're going?
This is not the time to be
worrying about things like that.
It's much more important that you
keep some room in your brain open.
Hmm?
I'm stopping this ship.
And you, my friend, are going to help.
Okay.
Hey, isn't this the...
Yeah, the blueprint of the
Flourish, this steamer. But how?
How are you able to get that?
It's not the original.
It's just something I copied from my
dad's workplace when I was a little kid.
But this is really amazing.
It's reproduced all the way
down to the tiniest scribbles.
You must have had a lot
of respect for your dad.
Kite?
Kite!
Kite, you must become the kind of
person who does things for others.
As for me, I was able to do
it with the sand steamer.
I wonder what you'll devote
your life to, my son.
I don't have it, Dad.
What the hell is someone like me supposed
to do for a living
where I can help people?
What are you getting all
sentimental on me for,
you little squirt?
Feeling better now?
We're going to survive. Got that?
Uh, yeah.
Why didn't it explode? Is it a dud?
That was freaky.
What a haul!
Now we've got some guns to play with!
When we get to the end, make a right!
Oh, I understand.
These are all voice tubes.
Yeah, but...
do you really think this will work?
Well, the ball's in motion.
We just have to see if they pick it up.
He got us, boss.
He's not human.
This is great.
Even better than a dime novel.
At last, we're actually
going to have some fun.
Let's see if our little
friend really sparkles
Attention scumbags if you slack
off till timeout, I will kill you.
Drag that blonde bastard up
here or else It's my time.
I'm at the starboard passenger cabins.
It's him.
It's the blonde guy.
Good.
Hold him right there
I'll send you some help.
That's no good.
I can't stop him.
He's hitting himself.
His speed is incredible Oh,
jeez, what a shoe of a fool.
All right, got him.
Now I'll be able to
figure out where they are.
But how will I contact you to let you
know where they're going to be, huh?
Wait, isn't this... It's simple.
All you have to do is talk
into it and I'll hear you.
I don't want to be caught in some
shootout in a narrow passageway,
so I'm going to be counting on your help.
Don't let me down, okay?
Hold on just a minute.
Where did you get this?
What are you doing with
this lost technology?
Technology just who the
hell are you anyway?
I'd explain it to you, but you
wouldn't believe me besides.
There's no time
Don't worry so much
about the little details.
See ya
Bash you okay? No guys.
It wasn't supposed to start like this.
I don't understand.
What's wrong?
I screwed up They're bleeding badly.
I have to help them. Help
them? What do you mean?
Are you serious?
Are you actually saying that you've purposely
avoided killing them the entire time?
Huh?
What the hell?
I don't understand you!
No matter how good a shot you are,
unless you shoot to kill, you're
gonna get yourself killed!
Well, I guess it is kind of
a stupid approach, isn't it?
I know that.
You're right, it's true.
It is very sloppy of me.
But you know what?
I made a promise.
If I put out even one flame of
life, it would make her sad.
There's something happening in the
central stairway on third floor.
Good.
Port passenger cabin team, head around
behind the central stairway quickly.
Everybody on floors one through five,
position yourselves around
each stairway and close in now.
What's that time?
Seven minutes left.
When you get there, you
should speed right across.
They're gathering above
and below you right now.
Roger.
That's stupid.
You gotta stop being so
soft with those bad lads.
No one's more than that.
Stop being so damn soft
with the entire human race.
I am betrayed, and they am betrayed, and
we all and a lot of innocent people die.
It's too late for us to go back
now, and they're too damn clean.
Then you should start over.
What the ticket
to the future is?
Always open.
He's broken past the
central engineers cabin.
He is good.
A real tough bastard.
But he's also got The devil's luck.
What should we do? Boss?
I don't believe that luck
has anything to do with this.
Keep going straight.
There should be a stairway on your right.
Take it all the way down.
Don't go anywhere else.
That's the only unmanned place.
Welcome to the party hall.
You arrived just in time.
I trust that my brilliant
directions were clear enough.
Oh, Kite, you've got to get
out of that room immediately.
I like the way you sparkled.
Very impressive.
I'm glad you're a worthy opponent.
Are you no longer afraid of dying?
We found him, boss.
It was the kid.
Get up, you pain in the ass!
You gave us a lot of trouble!
Looks like you're all out of tricks.
Oh well, it's a real accomplishment
that your rag team made it this far.
However, the simple fact is, reality
is almost never that beautiful.
I actually do feel for you.
Vaya con Dios.
That's far enough.
What are you trying to pull?
I've never been particularly
fond of this method,
but it seemed to be the quickest
and easiest way to get past you.
I am Meryl Stryfe from the
Bernardelli Insurance Society.
However, in some places, I happen to
be better known as Derringer Meryl.
Don't mess with us, little girl!
Um, hi.
My name is Millie Thompson.
Uh, let's see now.
I suppose for the time being, you
can just call me Stun Gun Millie.
How does that sound?
We're gonna let you off easy this time,
only because we don't seem
to have a lot of time left.
Now,
I expect you'll act like
a reasonable adult and
take care of them quickly
without screwing around,
Mr.
Vash the Stampede.
Vash the Stampede!
Well, my friend, it looks like our
time together is running short.
The ship's taking a real beating.
I doubt it'll last very long.
Well, what do you want to do?
How about you and your
guys go down with me?
I'll drop you right now, Clonty.
All right, let's find out just
who sparkles the most between us.
You idiots, stay out of it.
We'll settle it with
an old-fashioned duel.
I'm in, and if I win this
showdown, will you stop the ship?
If you won.
Engine temperature is abnormal, sir.
The hull is screaming.
All we can do at this point is bet on him.
He's our only hope.
I know it's rather
trine and old-fashioned,
but what do you say we start
right when this car hits the deck?
BIRDS CHIRP
Oh, no, Vash!
Are they both hit?
You stupid idiot.
That's what you get for jumping around.
I can handle that in the shape you're in.
Aren't you gonna finish him?
Hey, boss! Boss?
Maramita, shut up.
I didn't even shoot him.
He tore his own wounds open.
You should finish him anyway, boss.
You're too soft-hearted.
Hey, use those huge dynamos of yours.
Like I've mentioned so many times before,
a pain defended to the death
is a name worthy of respect.
Everybody, Vash won the duo!
Emergency brakes!
Hit them now! Aye, Captain.
It's no good they won't engage, sir?
Did the impact damage
the hydraulic system?
Unconfirmed, sir!
But I'm getting abnormal
pressure readings in the boiler!
If it gets much higher than this,
the entire hole will explode!
Force the engines to a
full stop immediately!
I can't
believe you were
fighting in that condition!
Are you out of your mind?
We have to get that looked after quick!
We've We've got an emergency!
What's going on?
There's been a system malfunction.
We've lost the steering.
What?
We need kite.
Is there a way to shut the engines down?
We'd have to power down
the system manually.
Where can we even do that?
I have no idea.
This ship is so old.
It's an engine room, too.
There's an emergency stop lever inside
the control system, but access is limited.
What the hell do you
know, you little brat?
I'll never forget watching my fellow crew
mate as he was killed
right in front of me.
I will not accept help from you
we will stop the ship ourselves!
Kite, what are you going to do, Kite?
Quit bugging me, I know.
The time has come for me to pay
the price for what I've done.
Only 4,500 yards left till the deadline.
4,000 yards remaining.
Okay, that's it.
All right, let's get it open.
3,500 yards.
3,000.
What's with this place?
It's like a cellar in here.
2,500.
It's way over there.
It isn't working, dammit! It won't punch!
There just isn't any way we can
get through this mass of pipes!
1,800.
Come on. It's hopeless.
There's nothing we can do.
We're not gonna make it.
Calm down. There's a way.
There's gotta be.
The emergency stop system
has been activated, sir.
How many yards do we have left?
800!
We're just going too fast!
It's too late!
Thanks to Mr.
Nasty's selfless act of
heroism, we were all saved.
Neon did that?
Now don't get the wrong idea.
I just paid off my wager.
The next time we meet,
it's no holds barred.
I'll take that life of yours. Count on it.
That smug jerk laid it on us
real thick all the way home.
So, on the first evening of Pebble,
From somewhere out of nowhere
drops upon the dreaming world
Sooooooooooo?
That song. Yeah?
I know it's an old song, but I like it.
It's a good song, so shut up.
Oh, yeah, right. It's a good song.
From somewhere out of nowhere
drops upon the dreaming world
It's the same song that she loved.
Hey, will you stop it?
You're making me cry!
AHH!!
What made up front of me, a-fif-fuckhead!
Oh, I meant you were hearing it!
Shut up, you flaky show-off!
What kind of flaky show-off?
That's why you're not gonna be anything!
Let's take care of them.
I met a lone man in the desert.
a traveling priest, Nicholas D. Wolfwood.
He smiled, and then he told
me that I'm a troubled man.
Faced with his all-seeing smile, there
was nothing I could say in my defense.
Did I meet this man
because I was destined to?
Or was it simply by a small gist of God?
The man's name is Nicholas D.
Wolfwood, a traveling
priest I met in the desert.